greenlightarticles.com 2011-12-05

# Green Light Articles

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Unique content is critical and Google made this clear with the latest search engine updates. Green Light Articles is the best way to create unlimited unique content without all the work. Whenever I build a niche site I always start with unique content and Green Light Articles is cheapest and fastest path to high-quality unique content. I highly recommend it!   
**Robert Stanley**  
http://robertmstanley.com/ 

* * *

The longterm success for any website is always determined by the quality of the content on it. GreenLightArticles.com allows me to get high quality content at very affordable prices and I cannot recommend them enough. Unlike some of the garbage content I have paid big money for in the past, content from GreenLightArticles.com is solid, is readable, and most important of all, it makes sense to the reader. Again, if you are in need of good content, I would personally recommend these guys. They get the job done and they get it done right - everytime!   
**Konrad Braun**  
http://empiremarketing.ca/
